OLATUNDE DAVID AKINROLABU

Python developer, data scientist

08064518483 Nigeria Horlamy007@gmail.com

Twitter: https://twitter.com/d_Holar LinkedIn: https://twitter.com/d_Holar

Professional Summary

Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals. Well-qualified data scientist is familiar with gathering, cleaning and organizing data for use by technical and non-technical personnel. Experienced working with vast data sets to break down information, gather relevant points and solve advanced business problems. skilled in predictive modeling, data mining and hypothetical testing. Offering 3 years of experience in improving business and academic operations. Highly organized, motivated and diligent with significant background in backend development, machine learning, data mining and deep learning.

Technical Profile

- Python (Django, flask)
- JavaScript (Node, Express)
- Machine learning
- GitHub
- MySQL
- Microsoft Office

Skills & Competencies

Backend Development

Experience in (Python, Javascript, Java and Php)

Experience in Computer Science Dissertation Writing

Web technologies, Data analytics and Modeling

Machine and Deep learning model implementations

Leadership Skills, Management skills And Excellent tutoring

Work History

PYTHON AND WEB DEVELOPER, 08/2020 - 02/2021 **Jethro Software Limited**, Ibadan, Nigeria

- Developed technical solutions required to accommodate specific user-facing assets
- I also helped in the documentation of software manuals and also help the debugging unit in testing and debugging software(s).
- Multi-tasked across multiple functions and roles to meet deadlines and organizational expectations.
- Developed webapps using Django, JavaScript and jQuery languages.

WEB DEVELOPER INTERN, 07/2018 - 12/2018 Computer Resource, Akure, Nigeria

- Department: Software Management
- Wrote custom HTML and JavaScript for existing websites.
- Worked closely with developers on creating new code.
- Prioritized and problem-solved several tasks concurrently with minimum supervision.

Education

Mayowa Nursery And Primary School - Akure Nigeria, 01/2000 - 01/2006

Oyemekun Grammar School - Akure, Nigeria, 09/2007 - 06/2014

Bachelor Of Science: Computer Science

ADEKUNLE AJASIN UNIVERSITY - Ondo State, 12/2015 - 11/2019

GPA: 3.85

• Elected as the Class Governor for Student Organization, and Tutoring in [2015 through 2019]

Master Of Science: Computer Science

Adekunle Ajasin University - Ondo State, 05/2021 - Current

• Elected as the Class Governor for the MSC class for Student Organization and Tutoring.

Accomplishments

- Delivered a public lecture on "Effects of ICT on Education" to the general Association of Akure North Local Government Students
- Participated in the 9th covenant university conference on E-business and E-Government in Nigeria (CUCEEN 2022) and presented a paper titled: Machine Perception of Political Manifestos in Predicting Performance of Public Office Holders
- Assisted over 70+ computer science final-year students with their thesis
- Developed and uploaded more than Three (3) web applications on Heroku web services
- Few of my code projects on my:-(https://github.com/onelove001, https://bitbucket.org/dashboard)

Certifications

Jobberman Soft-Skills Training

Python for machine learning and data science bootcamp (Udemy)

Python for backend web development Django (Udemy)

Web development bootcamp (MERN) stack (Udemy)

Papers

- Predicting NYSC mobilization period using Arima Model
- Machine perception of political manifestos in predicting performance of public office holders

References

Dr Olusola Ajayi

Lecturer in Computer Science (AAUA)

Phone: 08137044500

Email: ajayiprogrammer@gmail.com

Dr Oluwafemi Oriola

Lecturer in Computer Science (AAUA)

Phone: 08067007462

Email: oluwafemi.oriola@aaua.edu.ng

Mr Adebola Orogun

Lecturer in Computer Science (AAUA)

Phone: 08035676674

Email: orogun.adebola@aaua.edu.ng

Mr Fisayo Oyenuya

Senior Technical Consultant (Cahead Technologies ltd.)

Phone: 08152169703

Email: oyenuyafisayo@gmail.com